我睡着又独自醒来
I go to sleep and I wake up alone
当你离开时我总觉得更爱你了
I always seem to love you more when you’re gone
人来人往 但什么都无法让我笑
People come and go here, but nothing makes me smile
我仍感到孤独好久了
I still feel so lonely and I have been for a while
我需要你花点时间陪我
I need a little bit of your time
我需要你夜晚的一点片段
I need a little piece of your night
请关注我
Give me some of your undivided attention
然后我会给你我的一切
I’ll give you everything I got
我的一切
everything I got
我不是那种一直等你的人
I’m not the kind to be waiting on you
我需要保持我的自尊
I’ve got my pride to hold on to
你给我施了咒语 现在我在打破我自己的规则
You cast a spell on me, now I’m breaking my own rules
我已经熟悉了蠢货之间的游戏规则
I’ve yet to get familiar with the game of fools
我需要你花点时间陪我
I need a little bit of your time
我需要你夜晚的一点片段
I need a little piece of your night
请关注我
Give me some of your undivided attention
然后我会给你我的一切
I’ll give you everything I got
我的一切
everything I got
我从未来过这
I’ve never been here before
从未有如此触及我的底线
Never been this close to the floor
我尝试阻止它 我无可否认
I try to stop it, I can’t deny it
我迷上你了
You got me
我是你的
I’m yours
我需要你花点时间陪我
I need a little bit of your time
我需要你夜晚的一点片段
I need a little piece of your night
请关注我
Give me some of your undivided attention
然后我会给你我的一切
I’ll give you everything I got
我的一切
Everything I got